(Sheldon:)DEFCON 1 is a crisis.
How can five not be worse than one?
Well, Star Trek V, worse than 1.
(Sheldon:)First of all, that's a comparison of quality,
not intensity.
Secondly, Star Trek I is orders of
magnitude worse than Star Trek V.
(Raj:)Are you joking?
(Raj:)Star Trek V is the standard
against which all badness is measured.
(Sheldon:)No, no, no.
(Sheldon:)Star Trek V has specific failures
in writing and direction...
(Sheldon:)...while Star Trek I fails across the board.
(Sheldon:)Art direction, costuming,
music, sound editing.
You know what? Can we just
forget I said "DEFCON" and go?
(Raj:)Star Trek V.
SHELDON: Will you at least stipulate
that Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home...
...is inarguably the best?
I have three words for you:
Wrath of Khan.
(Howard:)- Thank God you're here.
- What's the emergency?
(Howard:)I got the Mars rover stuck in a ditch.
- Where?
- On a dusty highway...
(Howard:)...just outside Bakersfield.
Where do you think? On Mars.